wibki.com 2019-05-09

# Wibki | Unlock the Web

#### Information regarding the Wibki organization and web site: 

Wibki recognizes that your privacy is very important. Please read the information below to learn more about our privacy policy guidelines. Since this is a website in progress with continual additions and expansions, and because Internet technologies are constantly evolving, these guidelines are subject to change. It is up to Wibki's discretion to make any changes as it sees fit, and any such changes shall be posted on this page. 

You are advised to consult this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes. 

Wibki is not responsible for the content or the privacy policies of websites to which the site may link. 

Our principal activity entails a visual portal and bookmark manager. 

Our privacy policy covers Wibki and its website: 

Organisation Name: All My Faves Inc.

Web Sites(s): http://www.wibki.com

City: Tel Aviv

Country: Israel

At Wibki, we recognize that your privacy and that of your personal information is important. Below we provide information on what types of personal information we receive and maintain in our company's records when you use/visit Wibki, and how we safeguard that information. 

Wibki collects and uses personally identifiable information for the following reasons and purposes only: providing users with the services made available through the wibki.com including, but not limited to the service, to communicate with users, and to manage users' registered accounts, if and when applicable. 

#### Log Files

As with most other websites, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website ("Log Data" ). The information in the log files may include your IP address (Internet Protocol) , your ISP (Internet Service Provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser through which you visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time at which you visited our site, and which pages you visited within the entire Wibki site. 

We use Log Data to monitor the use of the Site and of our Service. We do not associate your IP address with any other personally identifiable information to identify you personally, except in case of violation of the Terms of Use. 

#### Cookies and Web Beacons

Wibki uses cookies to store information such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. If you are not familiar with what cookies are, here is a brief explanation: A cookie is a small data file many websites (Wibki.com included) carry to your computer's hard disk. Wibki does not use cookies to collect users' personally identifiable information. We use cookies as an improvement tool for the Company, the Wibki.com website and our offered services. More specifically, we use cookies as data information regarding users' site preferences and navigation behavior, and website traffic and referred visitor statistics (navigation between WIBKI.com and other websites). 

A session cookie makes certain site features and services possible, yet is only a session long, meaning once you log out or turn your computer off, the cookie ceases its activity and is removed from your computer. A persistent cookie stays in your computer despite disconnecting from your browser, and is used by the browser in re-visits to the web site. You can remove persistent cookies by consulting your browser support/help service. 

Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or manage your preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. One of the consequences might be users' inability to log in to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts. 

#### Advertisment

Wibki uses third party advertisements on Wibki to support our web site. Some of these advertisers may use web technologies such as cookies and web beacons on our site. These technological tools send participating advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information such as your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, information regarding your installed Flash software. This is generally used for geo-targeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or for showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites). 

AdWords Remarketing is a Remarketing and Behavioral Targeting service provided by Google. It connects the activity of www.wibki.com with the Adwords advertising network and the Doubleclick Cookie. You can opt out of the cookie tracking here: http://google.com/settings/ads/onweb/optout?hl=en Personal Data collected: Cookie and Visit Data. Place of processing: USA. 

#### Information Collected by Wibki

Although using WIBKI.com is free for everyone, users need to register in order to take advantage of certain services and features on WIBKI.com, such as the MiniFaves feature. As a registered user, you will be asked to provide us with certain personally identifiable information. Such information may include your computer's IP address, user name, password, email address, geographic location and local time, phone number, and any other details you choose to submit to us or include in your personalized MiniFaves page. 

By adding your own choice of sites to your personalized Wibki homepage, you allow Wibki and others to access and use it in connection with Wibki and otherwise in connection with its affiliates' businesses. You can mark content as private to restrict access and use to those users to whom you explicitly grant access. Your use of the content does not affect Wibki's right to access and use it in connection with Wibki or otherwise in connection with its affiliates' businesses. 

#### Use of Contact Information

We may use your contact information to send you updates and promotions of current and future Wibki features and offered services. Should you decide to discontinue the recipt of such information, you are welcome to unsubscibe via our updates and/or promotion messages sent to your email. 

Wibki has agreements with certain external service providers and other reliable and safe third parties for the Company and website's managment and maintenance. These include but are not limited to hosting and maintenance providers, database storage and management services, and marketing projects. As an WIBKI.com's user, your personally identifiable information may be shared with these third parties on a limited basis, meaning only for the purpose of performing and providing WIBKI.com's services and features. In addition, sharing that personally identifiable information shall occur, if at all, only after those third parties have made an explicit obligation to safeguard your privacy and ensure the security of your data. 

#### Confidentiality

Feedback and other comments and statements that you chose to submit to Wibki by any means - whether by e-mail to Wibki Customer Service, telephone, letter, or any other communication method - shall be considered nonconfidential. Wibki is free to use such information on an unrestricted basis. 

#### The ways in which we may use your information

We use users' collected information to improve our marketing and promotional efforts; to analyze site usage with statistics and data; to improve our content and product offerings, and; to customize the Wibki web site's content, layout and services, for the benefit of our users. We may use your collected information to service your account with us, including but not limited to investigating problems, resolving disputes and enforcing agreements with us. We do not sell, rent, trade or exchange any personally-identifying information of our users. We may share certain aggregate information based on analysis of collected information with our partners, customers, advertisers or potential users. We may use your collected information to execute marketing campaigns, promotions or advertising messages on behalf of third parties. Information submitted through the 'Tell a Friend' feature is collected and used in the mail which is sent to the referred person or 'friend' who was listed in the submission. 

By posting content, you are granting permission to Wibki and others to access and use it in connection with Wibki and otherwise in connection with its affiliates' businesses. You can mark content as private to restrict access and use to those users to whom you explicitly grant access. Your use of the content does not affect Wibki's right to access and use it in connection with Wibki or otherwise in connection with its affiliates' businesses. 

#### Links to other sites

Although Wibki provides numerous links to websites, this action is by no means any endorsement, advertisement for profit, authorization or representation of our affiliation with those third parties or featured sites, excluding sites and parties with which Wibki has a contracted agreement. Wibki has no control over any of the sites we feature anywhere on the website. Featured sites on Wibki may use cookies of their own or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personally identifiable information from you. Other sites comply with different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the personally identifiable information submitted to them by users. Please consult the privacy policies and/or statements of the other websites you visit. 

#### Wibki's Policy Regarding Children

Only users at least 13 years old or older may use WIBKI.com. Children under 13 are welcome to use the website under the supervision of their parents, legal gurdian or other authorized adult. However, Children may not sign or provide any perosnally identifiable information to WIBKI.com. If you are a parent or legal guardian who has learned that the child under your care is or has provided us with personally identifiable information without your knowledge and/or concent, contact us at [info@wibki.com](mailto:info@wibki.com). WIBKI.com does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. Should we learn of such a case, his or her information shall be removed immediately from our records. 

#### Your Feedback

Wibki welcomes your continuous input regarding our Privacy Policy or our services provided to you. You may send us your comments and responses to [info@wibki.com](mailto:info@wibki.com).
